workingadvantage.com 2012-05-01

# Working Advantage - Employee Discount Ticket Program

|  |  |   
---  

New Offers, Apparel, Beauty, Books & Media, Car Rentals, Cell Phones, Computer & Office, Electronics, Flowers & Gifts, Food, Go Green, Health, Home & Garden, Jewelry, Kids, Pets, Photos & Art, Services, Sports & Fitness, Travel, Travel-related, Canada, United Kingdom, Free Stuff  

Aquariums, Attractions, City Booklets, Comedy, Cruises, DISNEYLAND® Resort, Disney World® Resort, E-Tickets, Gift Cards, Golf, Hotels, Movie Rentals, Movie Tickets, Museums, Restaurants, Six Flags, Ski Tickets, Theme Parks, Water Parks, Zoos  

New York Events, New York Theatre, Atlanta, Austin, Baltimore, Boston, Charlotte, Chicago, Connecticut, Dallas/Fort Worth, Denver, Florida, Houston, Indianapolis, Las Vegas, Los Angeles, Minneapolis, New Jersey, Ohio, Philadelphia, Phoenix, Pittsburgh, Portland, Raleigh, Rhode Island, San Diego, San Francisco, San Antonio, Seattle, Washington DC, Wisconsin, Family Events, Sporting Events  

Anniversary, Baby, Birthday, Congratulations, Corporate Gifts, Get Well, Gift Cards, Graduation Gifts, Sympathy, Thank You, Wedding  
|   
Movie Tickets, Gift Cards  

| 

**Guarantee of Privacy**   
Your privacy is very important to us and we guarantee its protection. 

**Personal Information**   
All personal information you give us is kept confidential and protected with the utmost care, and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. We won't sell, rent or disclose any information that identifies you to an unrelated third party without your approval. 

We do not collect personal information when you visit our site unless you choose to register or complete a purchase. We then use this information to provide you with the service that you have requested or other value-added services from Working Advantage. For example, if you purchase an item, we will use your e-mail address to send you a confirmation notice and your address to ship you the package. We may also need to contact you via phone, postal mail or e-mail if we have other questions regarding your order. As a registered Working Advantage member, you may also receive special announcements and promotions but you may opt out of these mailings at any time. 

If you choose to subscribe to our mailing list, we will send you regular e-mail newsletters, inform you about new features, products or services, or changes to services. As a member of Working Advantage, you can review and change your personal information and subscription status at any time at My Account on the website or by calling us. 

**Credit Card Safety**   
Protecting the safety of your credit card information is also very important to us. 

We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your credit card information as it is transmitted to us. SSL is the standard in Internet encryption technology, and is a highly sophisticated method of scrambling data as it travels from your computer to our website's servers. 

We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. 

**Usage Tracking**   
We reserve the right to use aggregated, anonymous data about our users as a group for any business purpose, such as analyzing usage trends and seeking compatible partners. 

**Gift Messages**   
Working Advantage makes gift messages available on our website as a courtesy to our customers. Out of respect and consideration, Working Advantage asks that you do not use any obscene, profane, threatening or otherwise vulgar language in gift messages. Without notice to you, Working Advantage may, but is not obligated to, restrict or remove any and all content from a gift message that Working Advantage determines, in its sole discretion, violates these guidelines. 

**Limits On Our Abilities**   
The Working Advantage site contains links to other sites. While we carefully choose our partners, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. 

Although your privacy is very important to us, we cannot fully ensure that your private communications and other personal information will not be disclosed to third parties when required by law. 

**Changes**   
Working Advantage may modify this privacy policy at any time, and such modifications shall be effective as soon as the modified policy is posted. Accordingly, you should review the policy periodically, and your continued access or use of this site shall be deemed your acceptance of the modified agreement. 

**I'm just not comfortable ordering online. How else can I order?**  
**How do you guarantee my privacy?**  
**How do you guarantee the security of my credit card and personal information?**  
**What is the CVV2 Security Code?**  

Copyright © 2001 - 2012 Working Advantage®

|  |
